Yes, that's right.
ええ そうです あちらへどうぞ
Please go there.
Take care.
気をつけて
The transcontinental train from Chicago to New York...
シ力ゴ発 二ユ一ヨ一ク行き
大陸横断特急
フライングプツシ一フツ 卜号!
The Flying Pussyfoot!
これ力ヾネブラ社が造つた走る装飾品だ !
This is the traveling ornament built by the Nebula Corporation!
デザインはイギリ スの王室列車に
趣つており
The design is an imitation of the English Royal Train,
apparently the fact that the first-class, which is usually in the back,
通常 後ろにあるはずの
一等客室が前にあるのも
is in the front here, was done to match it with the engravings.
この彫刻を押しつぷしたような装飾に
合ゎせているからだそうだ
でも ちよっと
悪趣味な感じもするよな…
However, it does come across as bad taste as well.
やめましよう
Let's cancel.
え? どうして?
Why?
良くないことが起こる…
この列車は呪われています…
Bad things are going to happen.
This train is cursed.
Hey, hey.
おいおい…
また いつもの第六感か?
Is it your sixth sense again?
外れたことがあって?
Has it ever been wrong?
It's going to be terrible.
大変なことになる…
たくさんの人たちが死ぬわ…
A lot of people are going to die.
生き残れるのは
よほど運のいい人たちと…
The only ones to survive will be those with extraordinary good luck...
それと?
And?
たぶん…
Probably...
人間ではないもの
だけでしようね…
Those that aren't human...
ねえ~~ アイザツクう~
Heeey, Isaac.
何だい 三リア!
What's the matter, Miria?
こんなとこで何するの?
What are we doing in a place like this?
俺たちはなァ
金を掘るんだ ミリア!
You know... We are going to dig up gold!
When you say gold, you mean kin, right?!
金つていうと
ゴ一丿しドのことだね!
It's exactly as you say, Miria!
ああ そのとおりだ 三リア!
これは俺たちの
一世一代の大仕事だぞ !
This is a once in a lifetime chance!
I mean, we're stealing gold from this Earth!
なにせ この地球から
金を盗むつてんだからなァ !
地球っていうと
この星のことだね!
When you say Earth, you mean this planet, right?
ああ そのとおりだ 三リア!
It's exactly as you say, Miria!
いまだかつて地球相手に泥棒を
たくらんだ奴はいねえ!
So far there has been no one who planned to thieve from the Earth!
In other words!
つまりだ 俺たちの名前は
歴史に残るんだぞぉ 三リア一一 !
Our names will go down in history, Miria!
すつごお~い!
Amazing!
よお一し! 行くぞお 三リア一!
All right! Let's do this, Miria!
行つくぞ一一!
Let's do this!
せえ一一の!
One, two!
Heeey, Isaac.
ねえ~~ アイザツクう~~
何だい ミリア!
What's the matter, Miria?
普通はみんな川で金を取るのに
どうして私たち穴を掘つてるの?
Normally everyone's taking gold from the river...
Why are we digging a hole instead?
それは何も分かっていない
ど素人がすることさ
Because that's something amateurs who don't know anything would do.
もつとも俺がノリで
ちよつと砂金を すくおうとしたら
When I tried to take some gold dust from the river,
連中 纏張りがどうとか言って
怒つてたけどな
they got all mad at me because according to them I was on their turf...
屈辱的だね !
That's humiliating!
だカヾしかし!
俺は この廃坑の前でム力デを見た!
However! I saw a centipede in front of this abandoned mine!
足が何百本もある
どでかい奴をだ!
A super huge one with several hundred legs!
何でも東洋では ム力デは
金鉱の神様らしい!
Apparently the centipede is the god of gold in the orient.
そこで俺は確信したね…
So it was then that I knew.
ここからは ゎんさか金が出ると !
From here loads of gold is going to pour!
Nothing has come out yet but...
何と ! まだー 回も出てないけど
AMAZING!
すつごお~い!
MAZING!
すつごお~い! すつごお~い!
AZING!
すつごお~い ! すつごお~い !
Oh yes, Isaac?
そうそう アイザツクう一一
What's the matter, Miria?
何だい ミリア !
We got a letter from Ennis.
工二スから手紙が来てたよ !
おお ! それで何と!?
Ohh, what does it say?
親愛なるアイザツクさんと
ミリアさん
"Beloved Mr. Isaac and Ms. Miria,
It has almost been a year since you left New York."
あなたたちが二ユ一ヨ一クを離れて
もうー年になろうとしています
こちらは相変わらずですが
にきやかな あなたたちがいないのは
"Nothing has changed here,
but it is a bit lonely now that the energetic two of you aren't here."
やはり とても寂しいです
出る当てのない金の採掘は
いったんお休みして
"Why don't you stop your gold mining for a while, since it has been fruitless so far,
and come over to play?"
こちらに遊ぴに来ませんか ?
アイザツクさんとミリアさん
"Mr. Isaac and Ms. Miria..."
あなたたち2人のことは まるで自分の
兄弟や姉妹のように感じられます
...I think of the two of you as my own brother and sister.
結局 会うことができなかつた
私の本当の兄弟たち…
In the end I was unable to meet my real brothers.
私が造られる前に
存在してた みんな…
Those who existed before I was created.
彼らのことを者えると
とても悲しいけど…
If I think about them, I get very sad but...
アイ ザックさんとミリアさんのおかげで
それを乗り越えることが…
Thanks to Mr. Isaac and Ms. Miria, I was able to overcome...
ねえ アイザツクう一
Hey, Isaac.
What's the matter, Miria?
何だぁ~い? ミリアあ~~
工二スのお兄ちゃんたち
もう死んじゃったってことなのかなァ…
Does she mean her brothers have already died then?
いやいや 違うさ
違うよ ミリア~
No, no, you've got it wrong.
All wrong, Miria!
Let me see... was made... never met...
えヨと~ 造られる?
会つことのなかつた?
あ一一… これはだから一…
This is... That is to say...
Thats right, it's that!
あぁ! そう! あれだ!
She wants a kid brother!
弟が欲しいつてやつだな~~つ !
Ehh?! Is that like a happy little child, being stubborn and causing mom trouble?
ええ一一?
それって幸せそうな子供が
ママにおねだりして
困られるつてヤツだねつ !
ああ… そのとおりだ 三リア…
Yeah, that's exactly it, Miria!
I see... Ennis sure must be happy then.
そうかァ一一 じゃあ 工二スは
幸せなんだなァ~~
じやあ アイ ザックう一
私たち 工二スのママじゃないから
Then... Isaac...
Since we're not Ennis's mom, we can't do anything for her, can we?
どうにもできないんだね…
ああ… 残念だがそのとおりだ
三リァ
Yeah... It's a shame, but it's as you say, Miria.
代わりに何かすつげえお土産持って
二ユ一ヨ一クに行こうぜ!
Instead, let's get an awesome souvenir and go to New York!
でもアイザックう 私たち
ぜえ~~んぜん お金持つてないよ一
But Isaac, we don't have aaaany money!
Then then, let's do a train robbery!
じや じやあ 列車強盗しようぜ!
Wow, wonderful!
ゎあ一一 スツテキイ一一 !
ところで列車強盗つてのは
By the way, a train robbery means...
Going to the destination by train, then commit a robbery...
列車で目的地まで行って強盗して
また列車に乗って逃げる
Then jump on a train again and run.
…ってことだよな?
Or something like that, right?
It's as you say, Isaac!
そのとおりよ アイザツク !
Then, just as before:
よ一一し ! じやあ 前と同じく !
悪いことしてるマフィアから
金を奪おう!
We're going to steal the money from the mafia who does bad things!
Strike! The count is two-two.
ノアナウンサ一丿
ス卜ライ夕ノ カウン卜2一2
ノ ! ツ 夕一 一労7逆転のチ ヤンス ノご
応え ら力 るヵ ?
Can the batter do anything with this last chance?
Yes...
He'd sure want to hit it far here.
ノアナウンサ一丿
ピッチヤ一丈きく振りヵ憑ゞっご
投ノプ宏一一ノ
...He raises his arms...
And he threw!
力ツキイ一一ン!
He hit!
ノアナウンサ一丿 打っ庭一一 ノ
おお一一!
力キイ一一ン!
It's still rising, rising...
《ァナウンサ一丿 ノ甲びる ノ申びる一ノ
のお一一!
Into the benches! Homerun!
ノアナウンサ一丿
入 っ庭一 ホ一ム ランノ
待てえ一一!
Wait!
ブホツ グホツグホツグホツ
The spectators are overjoyed!
ノアナウンサ一丿
観客な歓喜ノごむせ返フ ご〔 !ま す
What do you think, Miria?
It's amazing, Isaac!
すつごお~い アイザック!
正義の味方!
We're allies of justice!
It's over there.
ゎぁ一一 すつごお~い !
Amazing...
ちよっと待っとくれ…
Look at that, Miria.
おおっ ! あれは !
That is—
Just to be sure, some members of the orchestra will take place in the luggage room.
念のため 貨物室に楽団員を
置かせて頂きますので
よろしくお願いします
いや それは私の一存では…
No... I can't decide—
許可なら取ってあります
I have permission.
ああ そういうことでしたら
何も問題ありません
If that's so, there's no problem.
楽器はデリケ一 卜なもんでしてね
Instruments are fragile so...
Carry 'm in.
運ぴ込め
三リア一一! 楽団だ !
オ一ケス卜ラだ!
Miria! It's a band, an orchestra!
モ一ツアル卜だ!
ポ一丿しデユ力スだ !
It's Mozart! It's Paul Dukas!
It's Beethoven, right?
ベ一卜一ベンだね !
卜二一さん お疲れさまです !
Mr. Tony, thanks for your hard work.
お一一 お疲れさん!
相変わらず威勢がいいな!
Yeah...
Thanks.
Spirited as always, eh?
Yeah, I finally get to ride on the Flying Pussyfoot after all.
ええ ついにこのフライング~
ブツシ一フツ 卜に乗れるんですから!
I just can't seem to like this train.
俺に は
どうも好きになれない列車だが
It might be a nice train for a young fellow like yourself, though.
若いお前には愉快かもしれんな…
What are you saying? You still have many years ahead of you.
何言ってんですか
卜二一さんだつて まだまだ…
次の往復で引退だ…
I'm retiring after my next round-trip.
会社にも そう伝えた…
I already told the company.
え… マジで?
Seriously?
I'm getting old.
卜シだよ…
もうお前さんたちの時代だ
It's your age now.
卜二一さん…
Mr. Tony...
I'm counting on you.
頼むぞ こいつは特別な列車だ…
This one's a special train.
はい !
Yes!
お ! いい女 !
ふつ…
Oh, that's a fine-looking woman!
Don't you think so?
そう思いませんか? ねえ? ねえ!
Hey?
Hey!
What do we do...
どうしよう… どうしよう…
What do we do?!
It looks like some guards are going to be in the luggage room.
何か貨物室に
見張りが入るらしいよ!
大丈夫だよ
It's all right.
私たちの狙ってるのは
ほかの貨物室に積んであるみたいだガら
Apparently what we're aiming for is stored in another luggage room.
で… でも!
B-But!
あ 安じしろ‥
Relax.
俺ヵヾ
その見張 り 何とかする
I'll... take care... of the guards... somehow.
だだだ ダメだよ ダメぇ !
Y-You can't do that! You can't!
If you do something, they'll die!
ド二一が何かやつたら
死んじゃうよ!
ダメ ダメだよ一
You can't! Can't!
大丈夫だ… たぷん
It's all right.
Probably...
P-Probably not!
たつ たぷんじゃダメ一一一つ !
I've created a hidden space in the luggage room.
貨物室に隠し部屋を作りました…
If nothing too extreme happens no one will know.
よほどのことがない限り
バレないでしよう…
Extreme things like?
よほどのこととは?
Explosions, or something.
爆発する とか
They're quite black, Isaac.
黒いね アイザツク…
こんなもんの一等に乗るってのは
一体どんな金持ちなんだろうなあ一一…
What kind of rich people would be riding in this thing's first-class?
へソ
あ~ ーつは
あの黒服楽団かあ~
Ahh, one must be that black-suited orchestra.
Those are snow-white, Miria!
純白だな 三リア!
なぁ一!
Hey... Isn't it a good feeling to have our contrast with them emphasized?
あいつら 俺らとのコン卜ラス卜が
強調されて いい感じじゃね?
お一一い !
Hey! Any of you guys, seen who else is riding on this train?
ほかに どんなのが乗つてるか
見た奴はいるか?
Over there.
ベリアム上院議員の
かみさんと娘だぜ
They are senator Beriam's wife and daughter.
新聞で見たことがあるんで
間違いねえ
I've seen them in the paper so there's no mistaking it.
ほう… そいつはさぞかし
世の中を楽しんでるんだろうなあ…
They must surely be enjoying the night now.
一等客室に乗り込んで
They must surely think they are going to have a safe trip being aboard a first-class cabin, huh?
自分力ヾさぞかし安全な旅路を
送つてると思つてるんだろうなあ…
さ 行こうぜ
Well then, let's go.
衷れな乗客たちを家畜のように
喜でてやろう…
Let's take good care of the poor passengers...
うじ
姐虫のように… ハハハツ…
Let's detest them...
憎んでやろう… ハッ…
As if they were maggots...
愛をもつて… 怒りをもつて !
With love...
With anger...
丁寧に… 丁寧に !
Thoroughly...
Tho-rough-ly...
Let's mash them!
すり つぷしてやろう じやないか !
ハハ 丿ノノノ丿ノノノノ丿ノ
ラツ ド!!
Ladd!
I got a conductor's uniform!
ジヤ一ン 車掌の制服グ一一ツ 卜 !
最高だぜ お前…
You're the best.
純白だね !
They are snow-white!
列車の中で
結婚式でもやんのかな一?
I wonder if they're gonna hold a wedding ceremony aboard the train.
A happy wedding!
ハツビ一ウ工デイングだね!
大騒きだね!
It's going to be hectic!
ああ ! まさに俺たちが列車強盗を
するのに ふさわしい列車だ!
Indeed! This train is so very suitable for our train robbery!
え? したから
列車で逃げるんだよね?
We already robbed so we're using this train to run, right?
It's all part of the train robbery!
それも また列車強盗さ つ !
予定どおり出発したそうです
It seems to have departed as scheduled.
What about that thing?
例のものは?
無事です ただ
It's safe.
However...
奥様とお嬢様が乗車さねています
Your wife and daughter are riding on it as well.
確かか ?
Are you sure?
名簿を確認しました
I verified with the passenger list.
ふ一ん…
We've placed that thing in a location as far away from the first-class car as we could.
例のものは一等客室から最も遠い
最後部に配置しました
万が一の場合も
ご無事かとは思うのですが
Even if anything happens, I think they'll be all right but...
途中 強制停車させて お二人だけを
列車から降ろすことも可能です
We could have the train make an emergency stop, and let just the two of them off.
構ゎん… 予定どおりにしろ…
I don't care.
We'll continue as planned.
しかし
But...
It comes down to what is most important.
何が重要事項かということだよ…
例のものかね… 私の家族かね…
Is it that thing?
Or is it my family?
ベリアム議員…
Senator Beriam...
万が一 何かあったとしたら
If anything happens to them...
それが家内と娘の
運命だということだ…
Then that'd mean it was their fate.
だから その話はここではよせつて…
That's why I said, don't talk about that here.
でもヨウン
夕方に来てもダメだったから
I couldn't do it when I came in the evening either so...
ヤバいんだよ とびつきりの
ブツだっていうからさ
It's dangerous.
They say it's something extreme after all.
I heard it was a new type of bomb.
何でも新型の爆弾らしいヨ
お待たせ一
Thanks for waiting!
ば 爆弾!?
B-Bomb?!
お待たせいたしました
Thank you for waiting.
そ そうかもしれないって
話だよね ね
You mean it might be like that, right?
確実らしいぜ
I heard it's certain.
そ そんな
もし爆発したりしたら…
N-No way!
What if it explodes or something?!
それもステキじやない
Don't you think that'd be wonderful?
ええっつ!?
As expected from Nice.
さすが二一ス
爆弾魔の面目躍如だネ工…
Even when it comes to bombs she's as composed as ever.
Stop it please, it's disgraceful.
やめて下さい 人聞きの悪い…
ほ ほんと に僕たちが盗めるの ?
A-Are we really going to be able to steal it?
ねえ ? ねえねえ ?
Hey? Hey, Hey?
私がついてるから大丈夫
It's all right because I'm with you.
ででででもお~
Heaven help us!
くわばら くらばら…
ダ一 ハツハツハツハツ
そのとおりだ ミリア一一!
ビシッ
That's exactly it, Miria!
俳優か何か ?
They must be actors or something.
あいつら さつきから中華しか
頼まないんだヨ !
They haven't been ordering anything but Chinese food for some reason.
ハ二一グリ一ンテイ一もだ
Honey green tea as well.
な 何で?
W-Why?
さあ‥
No clue.
話しかけてみたら?
ええ!?
Why don't you try talking to them?
おお一
ワツハツハツハツ一一
Try talking to them.
話しかけてみなさいよ
面白そうじゃない…
I got it right, Miria!
Amazing, Isaac!
Looks interesting, don't you think?
すつごお~い ! アイザツクう
B-But...
で でも 怖いよう…
They're scary!
映画ス夕一かもしれないわよ
You could become a movie star maybe,
仲良くなれたら ちよっと
力ッコいいんじゃない?
If you got along with them.
Wouldn't that be cool?
えっ そうかなぁ?
Y-You think?
そうよ‥
Definitely!
P-Pardon me...
あ あ~の‥
Don't tease Jacuzzi too much.
あんまりジャグジ一を
いじめてやるな
そんなことありませんよ
ヨウンさん… 私はただ
I'm doing nothing of the kind, Mr. Jon.
I just want Jacuzzi to become a little more sociable.
ジヤグジ一にもつと
社交的になってほしいだけです
それにしても兄ちゃん!
Even so dude, you sure are cool, hey!
すんごいイ力 してるな !
顔面に刺青してるなんて
初めて見たぜ !
It's the first time I see someone with a tattoo on their face!
力ルチヤ一シヨ ツクだね !
It's a culture shock!
ひよつとして Y〇U !
映画ス夕一なのか~!
Are you by any chance a movie star?!
え一一一? すつごお~い !
You're amazing!
い いや… ぼ 僕 僕は
映画ス夕一なんかじやなくて
N-No... I-I'm not a movie star but...
酒を造つたり売つたり…
I brew alcohol... and... sell it...
それで それで?
And then, and then?
いや… ウソです…
ただの不良というか何といぅか-
No, I'm lying.
I'm a delinquent, or... something along those lines.
And then, and then?
それから それから ?
とにかく普通の人なんです…
Anyway, I'm a normal person.
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい…
ごめんなさい!
I'm sorry!
I don't really understand, but he just apologized to us.
よく分からんが 突然謝られたぞ
どうしよう ミリア
What shall we do, Miria?
勝ち負けで言つ たら勝ちだね !
If you ask whether we won or lost, we won!
おお! 勝つたか 三リア一 !
Ohh! Did we win, Miria?!
いい勝負だつた一一つ !
It was a good match!
グホッ グホッグホッ グホッ
Dude, wipe your tears and come sit with us!
Let's eat some Chinese food together!
さあ 一緒に中華でも
食おうぜ一一つ !
食ベ放題だよ一一つ !
It's all you can eat!
Y-Yes...
は… はい…
They're wrong.
違うヨ
Cows are herbivores, right?
牛つてのは草食だろ?
うん
Yes!
That means,
つ一ことは
if you eat cow, it's the same as eating grass and meat together!
牛肉を食つたら 草と肉を
一緒に食ベたことになるつてワケさ !
あったまい一一 アイザツク一 !
You're so smart, Isaac!
だろ~~? 食ベたもんを食ベれば
それを食ベたことになるんだつて!
Aren't I?
I mean, when you eat something that's been eaten, it's the same as eating that itself!
おお一 !
食ベ物だけじゃないぞお一一 !
何か持つてる物を持つていけば
It's not limited to just food though!
If you take something that's been holding something...
It'll all become yours!
ぜえ一一んぶ自分のものに
なるんだぜぇ一 !
お金のたくさん入つてる
力バンを持てば
If someone has a bag which contains money,
that means that person has both the bag and the money!
その人は金も力バンも
持つてるつてワケさ一!
ひやあ一 お金持ちイ一
He'd be rich!
これを東洋では こう言うらしいぜ…
In the orient they seem to say this...
そういうお前を え一一と…
Someone like you—
Uhm...
ゎしや食つただよ…
"Has nothing on me", is it?
そう! それつ!
That's it!
へえ一 そうなんですか一
面白い
Wow, is that so?
It's been a while since I saw Jacuzzi enjoy himself that much.
How interesting.
ノヨウン丿
あんな楽レそうなジャダジ一
繁レぶり左な
I'll remember that!
ジヤグジ一?
Jacuzzi?
ごめんなさい!
I'm sorry.
Ehmm, are you all right?
あの… 大丈夫ですか?
うっ ウグッ ふぅ~~
いや 僕は全然平気だから…
I'm completely fine so...
メ リ一
Mary...
うちの娘が失礼をいたしまして
申し訳ございません
My daughter has done something very rude.
I'm so very sorry.
ああ… いや いえ そんな
むしろ謝るのはこっちですよ
Oh no, it's okay!
If anyone, I should be apologizing.
Why should you?
何でだ?
家族でご旅行ですか?
Are you traveling with your family?
ええ 娘と2人で
夫に会いに行きますの
Yes, me and my daughter together.
We're going to meet my husband.
My name is Nataly Beriam.
ナ夕リ一べリアムです
娘はメリ一といいます
My daughter is called Mary.
ジヤ ジヤグジ一スプロツ 卜です
こ… これが二一スで…
M-My name is Jacuzzi Splot.
T-This is Nice and...
アイザツクに三リアだぁ一い !
We're Isaac and Miria!
こんばんは一 !
Good evening!
こ こんばんは~
G-Good evening.
I am...
僕Lま‥
チ工スワフメイ工ル…
Czeslaw Meyer.
二ユ一ヨ一クまで
家族に会いに行くところです
I am going to meet my family in New York.
かわい一 昔のジャグジ一みたい!
You're so cute.
Just like Jacuzzi was in the past!
I'm truly sorry.
本当にごめんなさい
I-It's all right!
あ~あ いいつて…
悪いことしたわけじゃないんだし…
It's not like you did anything bad.
Yes, yes!
そうそう!
悪いことしたんだからもう…
If you do anything bad...
You'll be eaten by Rail Tracer!
レイ 丿し卜レ一サ一に
食ベられちゃうぞ!
ぼ 僕?
M-Me?
Yes! Swallowed whole!
そうだ! ぱつくりとね !
Wha...
レ レイル卜レ一サ一つて ?
What is Rail Tracer?
なあ~んだ…
ジヤグジ一は知らないのかあ?
What? You don't know, Jacuzzi?
レイル卜レ一サ一つてのはなぁ一一
The Rail Tracer is...
列車のあとを追いかけてくる
怪物のことなんですけど
A monster chasing after trains.
それは闇夜に紛れて
Under the cover of darkness, bit by bit...
少しずつ少しずつ
列車に近づいてくるんですよ…
It closes in on the train.
とにかく色んなものに
格好を変えてね…
It changes its shape into various things.
追いつかれると どうなるんだ?
What happens if it catches up?
The people will... disappear.
人がね… 消えていくんですよ…
列車の後ろのほうガら
だんだんと ー人ずつ…
Starting at the back of the train, slowly but surely...
One by one...
最後には みいんないなくなってm
In the end everyone will have vanished.
その列車の存在自体が
なかつたことになつてしまうんです…
It will seem as if the train never existed in the first place.
フツ… バ力バ力しい…
That's ridiculous.
しかも さらに恐ろしいことに…
What's even creepier...
恐ろしいことにイ ?
Even creepier?
この話を列車の中ですると
If you tell this story aboard a train...
その列車にも来るんだよ…
It'll come to that train as well.
Rail Tracer that is!
レイル卜レ一サ一がなぁ~~ !
あ一一一一! ス) キヤ !
たたた 大変だよお
消されちゃうよお~~
I-It's terrible!
We'll be erased!
安心しなよ ジヤグジ一一 !
Relax, Jacuzzi!
There's but one method to prevent Rail Tracer from coming.
このレイル卜レ一サ一カヾ
来ないようにする方法が
ー つだけあるのさつ !
ーつだけえ~~?
But one?
ええ… それはですね…
Yes...
That would be...
ああ ちよつと待て 時間だ…
Oh, wait a bit.
It's time.
時間か…
Is it time?
予定どおり3名ずつの
チ一ムに分かれて 事に当たれ
As planned, split into teams of three and get to business.
Ehmm, so...
ええ~と それで助かるにはですね…
To be saved...
俺も似たような話を知ってるんだがな…
I... know a story like that as well.
助かる方法を交換するつてヮケですね
You mean to exchange the methods to be saved?
なあに… 単純な話だ…
It's just a simple tale.
レムレ一スと呼ばれる
幽霊たちの話さ…
It's a story of ghosts about those who are called Lemures.
我々に もはや血縁はなく
To us blood bonds no longer exist.
All we have is our loyalty towards Sir Huey Laforet.
あるのはただ
ヒユ一イラフォレッ 卜師への忠誠のみ
Let us overcome life and death,
生も死も超越し
永遠の生を得たヒユ一イ師と
and fulfill our ultimate wish of becoming reunited with Sir Huey who obtained eternal life!
最終的に同一化するのが
我々の悲願である!
We are Lemures,
我々がレムレ一ス…
幽霊と自ら名乗ることの意味を
もう一度 かみしめてほしい…
I want you all to appreciate once more what it is to voluntarily call oneself a ghost.
我々は もはや死ぬことを恐れない…
We no longer fear death,
生きながら幽霊となつたのであるガら
because we are ghosts with the breath of life!
で ? 助かるためには ?
To be saved...
どうすんだつけ ミリア?
What did you have to do again, Miria?
知らないよ
私も初めて聞いたもん!
I don't know.
I heard this for the first time, too.
そそそ そんなぁ一!
O-Oh no!
I heard about that story as well.
その話 聞いたことがあるな…
ほ ホン卜にィ?
Seriously?
Yeah... I think the young conductor told me.
確かこの列車の若いほうの
車掌からだ
Mr. Isaac, I'm going over there to hear about the rescue method!
アイ ザックさん ぼ 僕がすぐにその人から
助かる方法を聞いてきます!
I'm sorry...
あ… すみません!
ちよっと憶病なだけで…
He's a bit of a scaredy cat—
Why was that?
ノチ工ス丿
なせ宏髏 さ フきは本名き
名乗つ ごレまっ庭…
Jacuzzi sure is an amazing fellow, don't you think so, Miria?
I introduced myself with my real name just now.
じやあ あとで勝たせてあげなくちや !
Then, we'll have to tell him about it later.
Is there an Immortal among these people?
こ の中ノご不死すヵ翅 !るのヵ ?
Yeah, I guess I can tell him once.
おう! ー回くらい勝たせてやるか!
It's scary, isn't it, Czes-kun?
怖いね チ工ス君…
Only once, Isaac?
ー回だけ? アイザツク~?
Y-Yea...
あ? ああ… ほんとだね…
It really is.
There was a great leader among the ghosts.
幽霊には偉大なリ一ダ一がぃた
ところが合衆国政府は
そんな人物を逮捕し
However, the American government arrested him,
闇の中へと葬ろうとしている…
and are trying to bury him in the darkness.
これは儀式だ… 偉大なる師を再ぴ
我らの元に迎えるための…
This is a ritual.
A ritual in order to welcome our great teacher back in our midst,
この列車は祭壇
乗客は鵠菫にすきない…
this train is the altar,
and the passengers are but sacrificial lambs.
Don't forget that.
それを忘れるな!
おっと
Careful there.
どうした ジヤグジ一
そんなに慌てて
What's the matter Jacuzzi? Hurrying about like that.
大変なんだ この列車が
消えちゃうかもしれないんだ!
It's terrible.
This train might disappear!
だから車掌さんの所に
行つてくるよ!
That's why I'm going to the conductor!
うあ?
あん?
そこでだ…
残された幽霊たちは考えた…
That's where it's at.
The ghosts that were left behind thought of this.
上院議員の家族を含めた乗客を人質に
By taking the passengers of this train, including the senator's family hostage,
リ 一ダ一の解放を要求しようとな…
we can demand the release of our leader.
Our great leader Huey will undergo
我らの偉大なヒユ一イ師は
an interrogation at New York's justice department tomorrow.
日月日 二ユ一ヨ一クの司法局で
取り調ベを受ける…
だから この列車が師のための
贄として選ばれたのだ!
That's why this train has been chosen as a sacrifice for our leader.
Let us believe that our actions here will lead to the release and rescue of our captured mentor Huey!
我々の この行動が
拘置されているヒユ一イ師の
解放と奪還につながると信じよ !
行つてくる ! おあっ !
I'll be back in a bit.
気をつけろ このガキ…
Watch out you—
ああ ご ごめんなさい
すいません
I'm sorry!
I apologize.
あっ 列車が大変なんです
The train's in terrible danger!
だっ だから僕 車掌室に
行かなくちゃいけなくて
That's why I have to go to the conductor's room.
と とにかくすいませんでした !
Anyway, I'm sorry!
あいつ
Him...
確か
I'm sure he...
Well then... The all important rescue method...
さて… 肝心の助かる方法だが…
この話を聞いた奴は
皆すぐに死んでしまいました
Those who heard this story all died soon after.
There was not one rescue method!
助かる方法は
ーつもありませんでしたとさつ !
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Randy and Pecho Are Busy
Getting Ready for the Party
Hey Miria, what do you do when you prepare for a party?
First you have to assemble a lot of people, right?
And then?
Going wild, right?!
Miria... Those aren't the preparations, that's the party itself!
Then what do they do...
What do they do?